W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  - Department of Transportation, 1967-1978, undated; 11
    - Automobile Safety, Correspondence and Reports, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Public Roads, Correspondence and Newsletter, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and Resolutions, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Summaries, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia, Correspondence and Statements, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia, “Summary of Comparison of Alternative Systems”, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1975 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Correspondence and Notices, 1977-1978 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Dulles International Airport, “Concorde Monitoring Summary Report”, 1976 May-1977 May (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Press Releases, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), “Twenty-Third Annual Report of Operations Under the Federal Airport Act”, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Federal Highway Administration (FHWA), Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Federal Highway Administration (FHWA), Press Release, 1977 March 29 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Grain Car Supply, Correspondence and Report, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Highway 190, Clippings and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - National Rail Passenger System, Preliminary Report, 1970-1971 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Press Releases and Resolutions, 1971-1975 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Printed Materials and Reports, 1969 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Printed Materials and Resolutions, 1970 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Printed Materials, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Rail Passenger Service Act of 1970 (RPSA), Background Information (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Seat Belt Usage, Correspondence and Petitions, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Transportation, “Fourth Report on the High Speed Ground Transportation Act of 1965”, 1970 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - “Summary of National Transportation Statistics”, 1972 November (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Brochures and Posters, 1977, undated (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Coast Guard Academy, “Bulletin of Information 1978-1979” (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Correspondence, 1967-1978 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1967-1977, undated (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Department of Treasury, 1932-1978, undated; 12
    Subseries XII consists of materials pertaining to the Department of the Treasury. Agencies prominently featured include the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, the Internal Revenue Service, and the Coast Guard (pre-1967). Some topics found throughout the subseries include revenue sharing, wage increases, inflation, price freezing, and the U.S. national debt.
    Folders in the subseries are arranged alphabetically by agency or material type. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
    - Appropriations Bill for Foreign Assistance, Information Packet, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - “Audit Guide and Standards for Revenue Sharing Recipients”, 1976 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Booklet, “A National Historic Landmark: Department of the Treasury”, 1972 October (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, Correspondence (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, Correspondence (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, Correspondence (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, Postcards, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, Statement, Rex Davis, 1978 May 4 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1971-1975 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Clippings, 1967-1970 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Cost of Living Council, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1975 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1977 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Correspondence, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Press Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Press Releases and Remarks, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Private Tax-Exempt Schools, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), Richard A. Zaun, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Leaflets, 1969-1974 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Legal Order, “Bernard Feinberg v. The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation and Alan R. Miller”, 1976 August (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Out-of-District Correspondence, 1975 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Out-of-District Correspondence, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Outline, Economic Tax Aspects of President’s Program, 1974-1975 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Pay Board, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - President’s Wage and Price Freeze, Clippings and Printed Materials, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - President’s Wage and Price Freeze, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - President’s Wage and Price Freeze, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - President’s Wage and Price Freeze, Opinion Ballots, 1971 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - President’s Wage and Price Freeze, Press Releases and Statement, 1972 March (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases and Reports, 1978 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Public Debt of the United States, Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Receipts and Outlays of the United States Government, 1978 January-April (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Receipts and Outlays of the United States Government, 1978 May-July (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Receipts and Outlays of the United States Government, 1978 August-October (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Report, “General Revenue Sharing and the States”, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Report, “State and Local Fiscal Assistance Act of 1972” (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Reports, 1932-1975 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Revenue Sharing, Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1972-1975 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Revenue Sharing, Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Revenue Sharing, Fact Sheets and Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Revenue Sharing, Guides, 1972-1976 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Revenue Sharing, Pamphlets, 1975 February-March (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Revenue Sharing, Press Releases and Statements, 1972-1976 (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - Revenue Sharing, Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Applications and Liaison Information, 1962-1965, undated (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Correspondence, 1955-1965 (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Press Releases, 1956-1966 (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Radio and Television Spots, 1961-1965, undated (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, Summaries, 1956-1966, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Customs Service, “U.S. Custom Service Aviation Program Personnel Requirements”, 1976 June 30 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Waco Banks, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Executive, 1945-1980, undated; 3
  Series III. Executive, the smallest series in the collection, consists of materials from and to the executive branch of the United States government. The White House and its Office of Management and Budget are prominent correspondents in the materials. Representative Bob Poage received most of the following correspondence and press releases during the Richard Nixon, Gerald Ford, and Jimmy Carter Administrations of the 1970s. The major exception is a folder of inauguration materials from President Franklin Roosevelt's fourth inauguration ceremony. Topics such as rampant inflation, Watergate, and clemency towards Vietnam War draft evaders are prevalent throughout. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence, 1972 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Vice President, Walter Mondale, Correspondence, 1978 September 8 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - White House, Correspondence, General, 1974 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - White House, Correspondence, General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - White House, Correspondence, General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - White House, Correspondence, General, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - White House, Correspondence, General (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - White House, Correspondence, General (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - White House, Correspondence, General, 1978 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - White House, Correspondence, Assistant to the President for Congressional Liaison Frank Moore, 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - White House, Correspondence, Inflation, 1974 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - White House, Correspondence, Inflation, 1975 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - White House, Correspondence, President Gerald Ford, 1974-1975 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - White House, Correspondence, President Jimmy Carter, 1974-1980, undated (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - White House, Correspondence, Presidential Clemency Board, 1974-1975 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - White House, Correspondence, Special Assistant to the President for Consumer Affairs Esther Peterson, 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - White House, Correspondence, Watergate, 1973 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - White House, Essay, “White Paper: The President’s Anti-Inflation Program”, 1978 October 24 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - White House, Inauguration Materials, Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1945 January (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1974-1976 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1977 February-March (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1977 April (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1977 May (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1977 June-November (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1978 January-March (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1978 April-June (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1978 July-November (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - White House, Reorganization Progress Reports, 1978 (Box 148, Folder 6)